<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<!--Race titles and descriptions-->
	<content contentuid="h3b50a476g26b0g46ffgb876g239463c0367a" version="1">Descending from celestials of the Upper Planes, Aasimar are a rare species often regarded as messianic figures throughout Faerûn. Compelled by divine purpose, their ancestry grants them unique abilities.</content>
	<content contentuid="haf93d995g7905g4663g9f14g1b95579af9f2" version="1">Aasimar</content>
	<content contentuid="h52d7266cg2c25g4c08g9104geb6f29877847" version="1">Descended from crusading angels, Scourge Aasimar inherit a burning desire to destroy evil wherever it's found. Their divine abilities are dedicated to offense.</content>
	<content contentuid="h91a77d44gefbeg4cd4g82b4g4ef0a77fc0f9" version="1">Scourge Aasimar</content>
	<content contentuid="h0e98342agff55g4afaga2fbg5e6251ae267a" version="1">Descended from guardian angels, Protector Aasimar, also known as Vigils, feel a need to safeguard others. Their divine abilities are dedicated to protection.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbd053ca5g5678g4239g9abdg4b08e63e676c" version="1">Protector Aasimar</content>
	<content contentuid="h784431d2g3a49g4f43g81a2g1333eb183a8e" version="1">Descended from fallen angels, or having fallen themselves, Fallen Aasimar experience impulses to destroy goodness as much as protect it. Their divine abilities are twisted into something altogether darker.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7c6af3a5ge868g45b8gac01g509380877d9f" version="1">Fallen Aasimar</content>

	<!--Heads-->
	<content contentuid="h15662ff8ga9ddg410bg8f01g14dc297f6666" version="1">Cracks 01</content>
	<content contentuid="hd8c0d07cgb938g469fg85e8ge5db112507fc" version="1">Cracks 02</content>
	<content contentuid="h3e88b235gde24g49f2g88eag5b87aecd560c" version="1">Cracks 03</content>
	<content contentuid="h3ec4a2a3g317fg46fegb3d0gd317f9d2162c" version="1">Cracks 04</content>	
	<content contentuid="heeb6f2a9g8cd7g4d6dg825bg34fa1163104a" version="1">Cracks 05</content>

	<!--Wings-->
	<content contentuid="h5b712fcdg285dg4077g800dg91447da2f552" version="1">Wings of the Protector</content>	
	<content contentuid="h56d3999fg5af0g49fbgac25g0950ced60a5f" version="1">Wings of the Scourge</content>	
	<content contentuid="hfbcc0df1g829dg489fga7a1g19e7a45b9521" version="1">Wings of the Fallen</content>	

	<content contentuid="h794e5c6fg17d0g4b7eg894dgad4573a18d8a" version="1">Radiant Soul Charge</content>	
	<content contentuid="h40b7ecf5g8c44g4839g8725g2765a68414bb" version="1">You may use this damagebonus once per turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h095f9fbeg7213g4ee2ga944g2b25d36b82d7" version="1">Mark Charge</content>	
	<content contentuid="h32d42a8fg2f00g4c7eg8f6bgefdf60a2b9fe" version="1">You may use this ability once per turn. The amount of times you can use this ability equals your Proficiency Bonus. You regain your charges on a Long Rest.</content>

	<!--Protector Abilities-->
	<content contentuid="hc63dd4b1g50f6g4064gad21gb2a5c8e0b84e" version="1">Mark of the Protector</content>	
	<content contentuid="hb67cf8d2g0323g483fg81aeg46461c2211ba" version="1">You may bless yourself or a target to take reduced damage equal to your Proficiency Bonus the next time they are hurt.</content>
	<content contentuid="he0025637gff81g4533gbf11ge84057fcce0d" version="1">Mantle of the Protector</content>
	<content contentuid="h9ea2caadgf8bag4269ga137gdc14e611491b" version="1">Your need to protect others manifests itself as divine power. You gain flight, and at the end of each turn, you and allies within 10 feet of you that you can see restore health equal to your Proficiency Bonus. Once per turn, deal extra Radiant damage equal to your Proficiency Bonus to one target when you deal damage with an attack or spell.</content>

	<!--Scourge Abilities-->
	<content contentuid="h989f2ecage565g4e72ga2c5g81e1d3f265dc" version="1">Mark of the Scourge</content>	
	<content contentuid="h0babd2c7gea14g4b2egb138g9079abe86152" version="1">You may infuse yourself or a target with divine ire, gaining your Proficiency Bonus as Radiant damage on their next attack or spell.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcfd55c57g688dg43bdg8f72gfb20137f1c3b" version="1">Fury of the Scourge</content>
	<content contentuid="hd64be7f7g8461g4eabg8a46g81eefbbfb8e5" version="1">Your righteous fury boils over. You gain flight, shed bright light in a 10-foot radius, and at the end of your turn, you and each enemy creature within 10 feet of you take radiant damage equal to your Proficiency Bonus. Once per turn, deal extra Radiant damage equal to your Proficiency Bonus to one target when you deal damage to it with an attack or a spell.</content>

	<!--Fallen Abilities-->
	<content contentuid="h828c4101g6508g4daag9055g394f13f47b7d" version="1">Mark of the Fallen</content>	
	<content contentuid="h20926a3bga055g47f5gae22g6eacb2522321" version="1">You may ward yourself or an ally with your inner darkness, forcing the next enemy who damages them in melee to make a save, or become Frightened for a duration equal to half your Proficiency Bonus, rounded down.</content>
	<content contentuid="h42b96546g51ffg453bg9930g4692f957113b" version="1">Embrace of the Fallen</content>
	<content contentuid="hb9cf9239g6903g4805g9078g991396c2a9b6" version="1">Unleash the darkness inside. Gain half your movespeed in flight. At the end of each turn, other creatures within 10 feet of you that can see you must each succeed on a Charisma saving throw (DC8+Proficiency+Spellcasting Modifier) or become frightened of you until the end of your next turn. Once per turn, deal extra Necrotic damage equal to your Proficiency Bonus to one target when you deal damage to it with an attack or a spell.</content>
</contentList>